Guide to the Stanley M. Issacs Neighborhood Center (New York, NY) Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Stanley M. Issacs Neighborhood Center (New York, NY) Records,
1959-1995.
Stanley M. Isaacs Neighborhood Center (New York, N.Y.)
21.5 linear ft. (in 48 boxes).
Columbia University Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Butler Library, New York, NY 10027.
4079920
History
This agency was established in 1964 by a coalition of settlement houses and philanthropic institutions to provide social services to public housing residents on Manhattan's upper East Side. Programs were later extended to all area residents, and include day care, Meals on Wheels and vocational counseling.
Scope and Content
The records include annual reports, correspondence, memos, minutes, program files, news clippings, administrative records and photographs. They document the agency from its origins in a committee led by the Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association to its work during the 1990s providing social services to thousands of East Side residents. The founding and early history of the Stanley M. Isaacs Neighborhood Center are best documented by minutes in Series II, showing the collaboration between the New York City Housing Authority and the Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association to establish the agency. They also offer the most comprehensive view of administrative, fundraising and program decisions from the early years to the 1990s. This series is supplemented by architectural drawings and plans for the community center in Series VI. Program records in Series V focus on the period 1980-90, with a few items from the 1960s and '70s. The agency's fundraising efforts are documented in Series III, which includes correspondence with foundations and individuals, donor lists and committee files.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 6 series:
Series I Administration
Series II: Board of Directors
Series III: Developement
Series IV: Executive Director Correspondence
Series V: Programs and Services
Series VI: Audio-Visual Material
Name and Subject Index
Subjects
Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association (New York, N.Y.).; United Neighborhood Houses of New York, Inc. (New York, N.Y.).; New York (N.Y.)--History.; New York (N.Y.)--Social Conditions.; Community centers--New York (N.Y.).; Human services--New York (N.Y.).; Public housing--New York (N.Y.).; Social service--New York (N.Y.).; Social settlements--New York (N.Y.).; Social work--New York (N.Y.).; Welfare--New York (N.Y.).; Administrative records; Annual reports.; Architectural drawings.; Articles of incorporation.; Budgets.; Bylaws.; Case files.; Certificates.; Contracts.; Financial records.; Fliers (printed matter).; Lists.; Memorandums.; Minutes.; Negatives.; Newsletters.; Photographs.; Plans (drawings).; Proposals.; Reports.; Transparentcies.; Child welfare workers.; Social workers.; Women social workers.
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Acquisition
09/22/1994 M-94-09-22 Records The agency Gift
Gift of the Stanley M. Isaacs Neighborhood Center, 1994.
- Series I Administration
  - Board of Elections, 1990-92 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - By-laws, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Certificates of Incorporation and Change of Purpose, 1964-67 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - City Council Redistricting, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Community Action Neighbors, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Resources, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Construction-Kuhn, Smith and Harris, 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Construction-Meetings, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Construction-Meetings, January-March 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Construction-Meetings, April-June 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - East Side Council on the Aging, 1986-88 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Women in Human Services, 1984-87 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Women in Human Services-Membership Lists, 1984-87 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1972-79 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1980-83 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1983-86 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1986-89 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements and Budgets, 1989-93 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Government Funding, City of New York:
    - Board of Education-Community Achievement Project, 1990-92 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Board of Education-Contract, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Community Development Agency-Contract, 1984-89 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Community Development Agency-Contract, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Community Development Agency-Contract, 1991-92 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Community Development Agency-Correspondence, 1982-92 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Community Development Agency-Proposals, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Community Development Agency-Proposals, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Community Development Agency-Proposals, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Community Development Agency-Proposals, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Community Development Agency-Proposals, 1990-92 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1983-84 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1984-85 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1986-88 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1989-90 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1990-91 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Department For the Aging-Contracts, 1991-93 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Department For the Aging-Correspondence,1977-93 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Department For the Aging-Proposal, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Department of Youth Services-Contracts, 1992-93 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Department of Youth Services-Reports, 1989-90 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Youth Board-Contract, 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Youth Board-Contract, 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Youth Board-Correspondence, 1978-84 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Youth Bureau-Contracts, 1984-85 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Youth Bureau-Contracts, 1985-86 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Youth Bureau-Reports, 1985-88 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Government Funding, Federal Emergency Management Agency, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Government Funding, State of New York:
    - Department of Social Services-Contract, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Department of Social Services-Proposal, 1992-93 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Division for Youth-Correspondence, 1978-81 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Division for Youth-Reports, 1986-88 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - State Education Department-Contracts, 1989-93 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - State Office for the Aging-Contracts, 1986-92 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Histories, 1970-84 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Internal Memos, 1985-86 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Internal Memos, 1987-88 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Internal Memos, 1989-91 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Knickerbocker Plaza, 1974-82 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Knickerbocker Plaza-Construction, 1975-78 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Knickerbocker Plaza-New York Junior League Task Force, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Knickerbocker Plaza-Reports, 1977-81 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Flyers, 1989-93 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - National Council on the Aging, 1989-91 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Not By Bread Alone"-Conference, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - New York City Housing Authority
    - Architectural Drawings, 1959-66 (See also "Series VI-Audio-Visual Materials") (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1978-94 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Lease Agreement, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Narrative Reports, 1979-88 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Narrative Reports, 1990-91 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - News Release and Flyer, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Statistical Reports, 1979-84 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Statistical Reports, 1985-88 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Statistical Reports, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Statistical Reports, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Statistical Reports, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Tenant Characteristics, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Opening Dinner, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Organization Charts, 1977-85 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Practices, 1973-93 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Policy Statement, ca. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Printed Material-Annual Reports, 1970-77 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Printed Material-Annual Reports, 1980-89 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Printed Material-Annual Reports, 1992-95 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Printed Material-"Centerline" Newsletter, 1980-82 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Printed Material-"Festival of Youth" Journal, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Printed Material-Promotional Brochures, 1965-94 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Report-"Stanley M. Isaacs Neighborhood Center: Critical Analysis and Strategic Plan," 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Report-"Stanley M. Isaacs Neighborhood Center: 1975 Self-Study," 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Scholarships, 1986-90 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Staff, 1976-93 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Staff Meetings, 1987-89 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - United Neighborhood Houses, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - United Neighborhood Houses-Core Management Project, 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Volunteer Opportunities, 1993-94 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Research, Inc., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Yorkville Civic Council, 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Series II: Board of Directors
  - Affiliations, 1980-93 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meetings, 1968 1980-84, 1989-94 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Committees--Adult and Family Learning Center:
    - Advisory, 1985-93 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Benefits/Special Events, 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Development, 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Executive, 1970-73 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Executive, 1974-75 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Executive, 1976-79 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Executive, 1980-82 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Executive, 1983-85 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Executive, 1986-89 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Executive, 1990-91 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Executive, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Executive, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Finance, Personnel, Administration, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Finance, Personnel, Administration, 1993-94 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Foundation, 1985-94 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Membership Lists, 1992-93 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Scholarship, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Senior Services Advisory, 1981-94 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Youth, 1982-93 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1977-92 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Development, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Former Members, 1989-94 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Giving, 1979-94 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Minutes-Swope/Isaacs Committee, 1960-63 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1963-66 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1967-70 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1971-73 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1974-76 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1977-79 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1986-89 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1990-93 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Profiles and Updates, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Rosters, 1975-94 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Series III: Developement
  - Appeals, 1980-88 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Benefit Committees, 1982-85 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Board Contributions (A-L), 1985-87 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Board Contributions (M-Z), 1985-87 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Donor Master File Report, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Foundations:
    - Abrons Foundation, 1982-85 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Achelis Foundation, 1968-82 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Emma J. Adams Memorial Fund, 1981-85 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Altschul Foundation, nd (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - American Express, 1969-85 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - J. Aron Charitable Foundation, 1975-85 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Astor Foundation, 1968-85 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Rose M. Badgeley Charitable Trust, 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - George Baker Trust, 1975-85 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Barker Welfare Foundation, 1975-85 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - BEA Associates, 1981-89 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - The House of Bernstein, 1976-85 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Blue Hill Troupe, 1976-85 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The Bodman Foundation, 1968-85 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Booth Ferris Foundation, 1976-83 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The Brick Church, 1970-85 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Brick Presbyterian Church, 1979-85 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Buckeye Trust, 1980-86 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Florence Burden Foundation, 1970-82 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Louis Calder Foundation, 1968-73 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Louis Calder Foundation, 1974-84 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - The Campe Foundation, 1971-85 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1981-85 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Chemical Bank, 1983-85 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Citibank, 1968-84 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Citizens' Committee for New York City, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The Clark Foundation, 1976-85 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1973-79 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Frank E. Clark Religious and Charitable Trust, 1969-85 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - The Robert Sterling Clark Foundation, 1975-78 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Columbia Foundation, 1984-85 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Consolidated Edison Company, 1978-84 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, 1974-79 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - December Foundation, 1968-86 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Cleveland H. Dodge Foundation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Dyson Foundation, 1982-85 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Congregation Emmanu-El, 1983-85 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Exxon Community Fund, 1979-85 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1970-86 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church, 1983-85 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Ford Foundation, 1967-80 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Fribourg Foundation, 1981-84 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Charles A. Frueauff Foundation, 1977-84 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Gannett Foundation, 1983-84 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Herman Goldman Foundation, 1976-85 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Goldman Sachs Fund, 1974-79 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - William T. Grant Foundation, 1985-87 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The Green Fund, 1981-85 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - David J. Green Foundation, 1981-85 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Mary W. Harriman Trust, 1971-85 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Charles Hayden Foundation, 1975-76 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Hearst Foundation, 1976-82 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - The Church of Heavenly Rest, 1977-84 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - The Heckscher Foundation for Children, 1964-85 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Herzfeld Foundation, 1965-84 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Holy Trinity, 1965-74 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Hyde Foundation, 1975-78 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - IBM, 1969-84 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - J.M. Foundation, 1980-84 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Joint Foundation Support, 1976-85 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - J.M. Kaplan Fund, 1964-81 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Henry Kaufman Foundation, 1973-75 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Kimmelman Foundation, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Korn Foundation, 1972-74 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Lavanburg Corner House, 1978-84 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Edith and Herbert Lehman Foundation, 1964-85 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Lincoln Fund, 1981-85 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Loeb Foundation, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Joe and Emily Lowe Foundation, 1971-85 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Lane Bryant Malsin Foundation, 1965-85 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Mandeville Foundation, 1977-85 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Gerard H. Mandes Fund, 1982-85 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Matz Foundation, 1965-84 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - J.M. McDonald Foundation, 1979-85 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Memton Fund, 1968-69 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Merill Lynch, 1971-85 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Metzger-Price Fund, 1974-85 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Barbara and Clifford Michel Foundation, 1972, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Mobil Foundation, 1983-85 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Edward S. Moore Foundation, 1979-83 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1968-85 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Henry and Lucy Moses Fund, 1972-85 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Muehlstan Foundation, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - National Westminster Bank, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - New-Land Foundation, 1970-85 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - New York Community Trust, 1983-85 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - New York Foundation, 1964-83 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - New York Foundation, 1984-85 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - New York Community Trust, 1969-74 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - New York Community Trust, 1975-84 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - New York State, 1984-85 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - New York Times Company Foundation, 1968-85 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Ray and Charles Newman Memorial Foundation, 1973-85 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Newsweek, 1982-85 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Nichols Foundation, 1969-72 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Edward John Noble Foundation, 1979-80 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Norman Foundation, 1965-81 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - O'Neil Foundation, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Louise L. Ottinger Charitable Trust, 1973-74 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Oaklawn Foundation, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Overbrook Foundation, 1972-85 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - William S. Paley Foundation, 1969-72 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Park Avenue Methodist Church, 1982-83 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Mimmie Parker Charitable Trust, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Penn Central Corporation, 1981-83 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation, 1981-84 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Pinkerton Foundation, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Jack and Lillian Poses Foundation, 1979-82 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Prospect Hill Foundation, 1983-85 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Ridgefield Foundation, 1981-85 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Edward and Ellen Roche Relief Foundation, 1980-85 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1964-84 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Helena Rubenstein Foundation, 1971-85 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Rubin Foundation, 1970-85 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Scherman Foundation, 1972-76 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - St. James Church, 1979-85 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Frederick and Amelia Schimper Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Evelyn Sharp Foundation, 1972-85 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Franz W. Sichel Foundation, 1983-85 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Silverman Charitable Trust, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Starr Foundation, 1984-85 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Surdna Foundation, 1974-85 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Taconic Foundation, 1965-85 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Tanenbaum Foundation, 1982-83 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Temple Schaaray Tefila, 1967-85 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Oakleigh L. Thorne Foundation, 1966-85 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Micheal Tuch Foundation, 1980-85 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Isaac H. Tuttle Fund, 1979-85 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1977-85 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - United Way of New York, 1973-85 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Upton Foundation, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - van Ameringen Foundation, 1972-85 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Vinmont Foundation, 1964-85 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Nina W. Werblow Charitable Trust, 1973-83 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Harry Winston Foundation, 1983-84 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Wooley-Clifford Foundation, 1971-84 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Yorkville Emergency Alliance, 1982-85 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Heartbusters Ball, 1984-88 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Meals on Wheels, 1983-84 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Phantom of the Opera, 1987-88 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - "Song and Dance" Benefit, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Thrift Shop, 1980-86 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Open Tennis Tournament, 1981-84 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Open Tennis Tournament, 1985-88 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Executive Director Correspondence
  - Contribution Correspondence, November 1986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 1-10 1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 11-31 1986 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, February-March 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Contribution Correspondence, June 1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Contribution Correspondence, July 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 1989 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, February 1989 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Contribution Correspondence, November 1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 1-15 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 15-31 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, February 1990 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, March 1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, April 1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Contribution Correspondence, May 1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Contribution Correspondence, June 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, July 1990 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, August 1990 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, September 1990 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, October 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Contribution Correspondence, November 1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 1-7 1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 8-15 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 17-20 1990 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, December 21-31 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 1-5 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 7-10 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 11-16 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 17-24 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, January 25-29 1991 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, February 1-6 1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Contribution Correspondence, February 9-14 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, February 15-28 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, March 1991 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, April 1991 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, May 1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Contribution Correspondence, June 1991 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Contribution Correspondence, July 1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Contribution Correspondence, August 1-19 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Contribution Correspondence, August 20-31 1991 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Contribution Correspondence, September 1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Contribution Correspondence, October 1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Contribution Correspondence, November 1991 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - General Appeal, 1987-88 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, December 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, January 1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, November-December 1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, January 1-15 1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, January 16-31 1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, February 1987 (Box 32, Folder 6)